<resources>
    <string name="app_name">G-Evolve</string>
    <string name="g_evolve_context">Where you can find E-Waste facility location and provides E-Waste Recycling solution</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string-array name="spinner_items">
        <item>Item 1</item>
        <item>Item 2</item>
        <item>Item 3</item>
        <!-- Add more items as needed -->
    </string-array>
    <string name="responsibilities">You are responsible for ensuring that your use of our services is in compliance with all applicable laws and regulations.</string>
    <string name="user_rights">You have the right to access and control your personal data. We will not share your information with a third party without your consent.</string>
    <string name="data_usage">By using our services, you agree that we may use your data to improve our machine learning models, and share with third parties for research and development purposes.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">We collect user data for the purpose of providing services, improving our products, and developing new features.</string>
    <string name="introduction">Thank you for choosing Agritech. By using our services, you agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions.</string>
    <string name="privacy4">4. Compliance with Regulations: Adhere to relevant data protection regulations and standards, such as GDPR, HIPAA, or local data protection laws, when disposing of electronic devices that may contain personal or sensitive information.</string>
    <string name="privacy3">3. Privacy Policies: Ensure that the e-waste management service provider has clear privacy policies in place regarding the handling and disposal of electronic devices. This should include provisions for data security and protection.</string>
    <string name="privacy2">2. Secure Collection and Transport: Use reputable e-waste management services that follow secure protocols for collecting and transporting electronic devices. This helps prevent theft or unauthorized access to sensitive data.</string>
    <string name="privacy1">1. Data Sanitization: Before disposing of electronic devices, ensure that all data is securely erased. Use data wiping software or physical destruction methods to prevent data recovery.</string>
    <string name="start_recycling_context">Transforming E-Waste Management. Your key to responsible recycling and sustainablity</string>
    <string name="about1">In India, the improper disposal of e-waste contributes to the alarming annual collection of 1.71 million metric tons. Locating trustworthy e-waste collection facilities remains a significant challenge, intensifying this environmental issue. The G-Evolve Web Platform is conceived to directly address this issue. Our platform offers a dynamic, user-friendly interface for individuals and businesses seeking reliable e-waste collection facilities.</string>
    <string name="ewaste_education">E-waste, or electronic waste, encompasses discarded electronic devices that are no longer in use or wanted. From smartphones to laptops, these gadgets have become an important part of our daily lives, but also contribute significantly to the global waste problem. The rapid advancement in technology leads to decreased device lifespans, causing an unprecedented amount of e-waste. This trend poses serious environmental and health risks due to the toxic substances found in electronic devices.E-waste can release harmful toxins into the environment, contaminating soil and water sources. These toxins include lead, mercury, and cadmium, which can have detrimental effects on human health and biodiversity.</string>
    <string name="about3"><![CDATA[Approximately 24.9 Mt of e-waste was produced in Asia in 2019, followed by 13.1 Mt in America, 12 Mt in Europe, 2.9 Mt in Africa, and 0.7 Mt in Oceania. E-waste output has dramatically increased due to the technology sector’s ongoing growth, shorter product life cycles, and customer demand for newer gadgets. Several significant decisions that affect the health and welfare of our planet must be made from the time an electronic product is conceived until its eventual recycling or destruction. Understanding the e-waste lifecycle & electronic waste management will help us all fight to reduce its negative consequences and promote a circular economy that puts environmental protection and resource conservation first. The life of e-waste begins with the spread of the newest electronic devices, which entice customers with their cutting-edge features and functionalities. The pull of newer models forces the inevitable replacement of older ones as technological development accelerates. As a result, abandoned electronics start their journey as e-waste, prompting the development of strategic management solutions to address this escalating problem. Beyond just affecting individual customers, this urgent issue has enormous implications for corporations, notably in the IT industry. Computer systems, servers, and other electronic equipment frequently undergo updates due to the unrelenting pace of invention, which significantly adds to the growing electronic waste stream. As soon as the electrical gadget reaches the end of its useful life, it has to be disposed of correctly.]]></string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">MapsActivity</string>
</resources>